GIOVANI FRANCISCO

ASPIRING SOFTWARE DEVELOPER / BUSINESS IT STUDENT / NURSE

+358 41 318 05 85 giofra.dev@gmail.com Espoo, Finland

https://www.linkedin.com/in/giovani-francisco/

https://github.com/GeeYouFra

https://geeyoufra.github.io/

PROFILE



I have the desire and determination to be the best of who I am.

I am a 2nd year IT student honing my skills as a software developer and looking forward to being part of your great company. I am looking for a part-time and work placement as well. If given the opportunity, I would like to work for your company. I would be very pleased to be trained and learn as I see myself diving into an adventure.

Aside from my 8-year involvement in putting smiles on people's lives, I seek to leverage my experience in this new life journey I am taking and am hopeful to be of contribution to your great company.

Filipino English Finnish

SKILLS

SOFTWARE

JavaScript HTML/CSS
Java Full Stack
React Node JS

PERSONAL OTHERS

Team player PowerBI
Adaptive QlikSense
Self-motivated VS Code
Eager to learn Eclipse

EDUCATION

HAAGA-HELIA AMK - Pasila Campus

2020 - 2023

Bachelor of Science in Business Information

Technology - BITE

SATAEDU Satakunnan Koulutuskuntayhtymä

2015 - 2017

Lähihoitaja / Practical Nursing

Benguet State University

2007 - 2011

Bachelor of Science in Nursing (Philippines)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Koti - Medi2019-2020

Licensed Practical Nurse
Espoo, Finland

Terveystalo Licensed Practical Nurse / Lähihoitaja

017-2019 Kotihoitotiimi, Hengityshalvauspotilaan hoito

Oulu, Finland

Licensed Practical Nurse / Lähihoitaja

Kehitysvammaisten hoito

Oulu, Finland

Staff Registered Nurse

Philippines

Staff Registered Nurse

Philippines

2019-2020

Terveystalo
2017-2019

Attendo Oy
2015-2017

Baguio General Hospital
2013-2014

Benguet General Hospital

2012-2013